# LUIS FELIPE ARAÚJO BOTH



Control and Automation Engineer. Seeking to use my abilities in coding and debugging to meet the business needs.

### CONTACT

luisboth@gmail.com

+55 67 99909 2746

Tiradentes Street, 2096 Ponta Porã

@luisfelipeboth

in @luis-felipe-both

#### **SKILLS**

**Spanish** 

Programming Python C# .Net Shell Script (e.g. bash, sh,) JavaScript HTML5 CSS3 (Grid, Flexbox, Bootstrap) Java C, C++ SQL LaTeX	
Operating Systems Windows Linux MacOS	•••••
Software & Tools Visualisation (e.g. matplotlib, mayavi,) Data handling/analysis (e.g. numpy, pandas, h5py, . Machine Learning (e.g. scikitLearn,) GUI Package (e.g. PyQt5, Windows Forms Git Jira Scrum Agile Microssoft Office	•••••
Arduino MATLAB/Simulink	
Languages Portuguese English	••••

## **ABOUT ME!**

Worked as software developer at Fraunhofer IPT in Germany using C# and Python as core programming languages, as well as visualization tools. Nowaday I'm in the middle of a transition to Front-end web developer. My main skills are C#, Python, Data handling and Data visualization tools, but not limited!

## **WORK HISTORY**

m 01/2022 - Actual

Freelancer Ponta Porã - Brazil

Freelancer projects using mostly C# and Python.

**10/2019 - 09/2021** 

Student Assistant at Intelligent **♀** Fraunhofer IPT. **Process Monitoring** Aachen - Germany

HMI programming with Python, C# and .Net; Machine Learning and Data Analysis.

**6** 05/2019 - 09/2019

**Engineering intern on Support** ♥ Hexagon Agriculture,

Florianópolis - Brazil and System Analysis

General programming with Python, JavaScript, C++ and Shell Script;

Support on On-board computers;

System and Report analysis.

**12/2018 - 03/2019** 

Rental Technician Snowshoe Ski Resort,

West Virginia - USA

Summer work and Travel Exchange Program.

**6** 08/2013 - 12/2015

**Q** CAECA - Academic Center of Control and Automation Engineering

Volunteer work at college.

Vice-Manager of Events

#### **EDUCATION**

Second Class of 2022

UFSC - Federal University of Santa Catarina, Florianópolis - Brazil

**Control and Automation Engineering** 

#### **CERTIFICATES**

The complete Python Bootcamp from Zero to Hero in Python.

## **PERSONAL SKILLS**

Teamwork	Hoi	nest	Punctual	Loyal
Written Communication Verbal Communication				
Motivated	Curious	Willingness to Learn		Self-Learning
Proactive	Dedicated	Flexible	Reliable	